annielytics.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy - Annielytics.com

We at Annielytis (umbrella company: Pied Piper Interactive, LLC) are committed to the protection of your privacy and will treat all of the information you provide through our website, including your registration information, with the utmost respect. Annielytics works diligently to ensure that it has taken all appropriate administrative and technical measures to prevent the unauthorized or unlawful use of your personally identifiable information, and to prevent any accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, such information. Annielytics will not sell or disclose personally identifiable information about you to unaffiliated third parties except in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Information

1\. The Annielytics website collects certain information about visitors, even when they are not logged in. Annielytics may record your IP address, the URLs of the websites and pages you visit (before, during and after your visit to Annielytics website), the times and dates of such visits, information about the computer hardware and software you use and other information that may be available. Also, Annielytics may place “cookies” on your computer to recognize you on return visits to enable Annielytics to enhance your browsing experience, as well as to collect additional information about you. You may adjust your browser settings or use other means to prevent cookies from being placed on your computer, but doing so may result in reduced functionality and a less personalized browsing experience.

2\. Annielytics may ask you to provide certain additional information about yourself, including your name, contact information, the organization you come from and certain other information that Annielytics may use to identify you. If you choose not to provide such information, you may not be permitted to access certain Firm website features, content or services.

## Use of Information

1\. Annielytics uses the information that it collects about you to improve your browsing experience by personalizing Annielytics website to your interest and also to help Annielytics select content and services that you may find interesting and useful. Information about the content you visit and services you use may be used alone or in conjunction with information collected from other users to help Annielytics tailor Annielytics website and its other products and services to better suit the needs and interests of you and other users.

2\. Information that you provide may also be used as part of Annielytics’s effort to keep you informed about events, and selected products and services that may be of interest to you. In some cases, Annielytics may contact you with information from carefully selected third parties, but Annielytics will not provide information to third parties for such purposes. In other cases, your information might be shared with a third party pursuant to a process that contemplates such sharing but which you knowingly initiate.

3\. Annielytics reserves the right to disclose any information that it obtains through Annielytics website to appropriate governmental or regulatory authorities, if required by law or any governmental agency.

## Transfers of Information

From time to time, Annielytics may disclose information about you to carefully selected service providers that Annielytics may engage to host website or to provide other services. Annielytics will require all such service providers to use the information solely to provide the specified services, and otherwise to conform to the requirements of this Privacy Policy. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, Annielytics will not provide your information to third parties for any other purpose, including marketing.

## Additional Services

From time to time, Annielytics may offer additional services through Annielytics website. In some cases additional services may be subject to alternative terms of use (as identified by Annielytics), and your use of any such services will constitute your acceptance of such alternative terms of use. Unless otherwise stated, such alternative terms of use shall apply to supplement this Agreement and in the context of any conflicting terms, this Agreement shall govern with respect to Annielytics websites, content and services, excepting only those services which are expressly covered, and then only to the extent so expressly covered, by such alternative terms.

## Information Sent by Way of the Website is Not Secure

Any information sent to Annielytics by Internet, e-mail, or through the website is not secure and is done so on a non-confidential basis. Any information you send Annielytics over the Internet, either through Annielytics’s website or via email is done at your own risk.
